Where are you?
Found you!
Hup!
I caught you!
A sadism trial?
I've made some poisoned apples.
Oh?
We're going to have Lady Doux hand
these out in a human village.
Once Lady Doux sees the humans
who eat these writhe in agony,
she should awaken to her demonic
instinct: a sadistic heart.
I see...
Looting, sadism, destruction, killing...
Every evil impulse or desire is
a demon's justice and instinct.
Doux should have those impulses
and desires within her.
Very well.
Let's not waste any time.
Lady Doux! We will take
these for your next trial—
I'm going somewhere wearing this?
Yes, you are. It looks great on you, Doux!
So cute! You're the cutest
in the world, Doux!
THE DIVINE MESSENGER IS
TOO MUCH TROUBLE!!
"The Divine Messenger Is
Too Much Trouble!!"
Your Majesty! This isn't some field trip!
Why is she wearing that hood?
I'm aware of that. This
is for her protection.
Very well, then.
Here, Lady Doux. Take these.
They look yummy!
Yes, but these are no ordinary
apples. They're poisoned...
Lady Doux! I just said they're poisoned!
Poisoned apples?
They are not delicious.
They are meant to torment.
Tor...ment...?
You just need to hand these
out to the humans, Lady Doux.
Once you're able to do that, you'll
become a full-fledged demon, Doux.
Really?!
Yes.
This time... This time,
it'll absolutely work!
Lady Doux just has to hand these
poisoned apples out to the humans.
Then she'll naturally awaken
to her sadistic instincts.
Any demon would be elated to
watch a lower being suffer!
Kitty!
Ah! Lady Doux!
You're not allowed to save anything!
Bye-bye!
This is the village where
your trial will take place.
I've chosen a very poor village to
heighten your chances of success.
Listen well.
You will say these are normal apples
and have them eat them.
Okay.
You absolutely must not tell them they
are poisoned or that you are a demon.
Got it!
Then...
Please have mercy!
Please have mercy, Lord Aeshma!
What's this?
A village like this has a ruler?
At this rate, my daughter
will starve to death.
Please show us some grace!
You...
Here.
Th-Thank you very—
Who do you think you are, huh?
I am Aeshma, a divine messenger, the one
protecting your village from the demons.
In return, you're offering
me all of your food.
Wasn't that our deal?
That guy's a divine messenger?
No. Divine messengers,
the angels, live in heaven and have
wings and a halo over their heads.
What's a halo?
They have a donut-shaped thing
floating above their heads.
A donut?!
So someone without wings or a halo
like him is not a divine messenger.
You can't be serious!
No divine messenger would abandon a
starving child to fulfill his own greed!
That's right! We can't take this anymore!
We definitely showed up at the wrong time.
I'd like to avoid any
trouble during the trial.
Lady Doux, let's give up on
this village and try another...
Wait, Lady Doux?!
Traitors will not be shown
mercy. They will be punished.
Now, who wants to be punished first?
Does anyone want an apple?
I beg of you, please learn some restraint!
We clearly shouldn't be
butting in right now!
Wh-Who the heck are you?
Where'd you come from?
Over there.
I wasn't asking the literal direction!
I'm asking where you live.
Doux lives in the demon castle.
The demon castle?!
Wha?!
Th-Then are you a demon?!
Big Sister Jahi told me I
wasn't allowed to say that.
You basically just admitted it!
What's a demon like you doing here?
I'm gonna give out apples.
Apples?
Those apples! May we have some?
Who gave you permission to speak?
We won't let you hurt them!
Oh?
I wondered how this would turn
out, but it's not going so bad.
Now, Lady Doux! Give the
humans the poisoned apples
and awaken your demonic instinct.
Do you like torment apples?
Torment...?
I guess these are torment apples.
I've only eaten yummy apples before.
Do you like torment apples?
No... I don't want any torment...
I see...
Lady Doux! Don't give up so soon!
Man, I love every moment
I torment these traitors.
I love it so much! I don't
know what to do with myself!
You like it?
Huh?
Then I'll give you these.
Wait, really?!
Hmph.
I guess you fear me
even if you're a demon.
I'll spare your life
for being so obedient.
Hey, this is great!
There's no way I'd let
those traitors have these!
GUUURGLE
My stomach... Ow, ow, ow!
What are these?!
They're torment apples!
You tricked me?! You
won't get away with this!
Whoa.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
It's Papa!
I applied a teleportation function
on the hood for emergencies.
It looks like it works!
Those travelers defeated
the divine messenger!
Hm? Divine messenger?
This guy's an angel?
No, no. He was just calling himself that!
Really?
Yes. Look. He has no halo or wings.
Hm... I see.
We've been freed!
Hooray for our hero!
What?!
Looks like the trial was
also a huge success, Jahi.
How so?!
We demons are being treated
as heroes by these humans!
But she was able to hand out
those apples, wasn't she?
Then perhaps Doux's sadistic instinct has
begun to awaken within her heart, too.
Here! Have a yummy one!
Wow...
It's so good!
Thank you so much!
I guess the trial failed.
Well, no matter.
Villagers! I am the Demon King Ahriman!
This village is now under my protection!
I will make sure you are not eaten
by monsters and even give you food!
In return, you will work for me!
I'll treat you better than
this "divine messenger."
Ahriman!
Lady Doux!
Lady Jahi!
Well, all's well that ends well!
Well!
This is all wrong!
THE DIVINE MESSENGER (THE REAL ONE)
IS TOO HOT-HEADED!!
"The Divine Messenger (The Real
One) Is Too Hot-Headed!!"
And then they...
Wh-What?
We have come to save you.
We are angels.
Essentially, we are divine messengers.
What is the matter?
We're sick of divine messengers.
But we're real ones!
You literally saw us come
down from heaven just now.
We heard that demons have
taken over this village.
We will help you escape.
You say that, but we don't exactly
hate our lives right now.
It's much better than with
that last divine messenger.
Mr. Ahriman and Ms. Jahi are pretty nice.
Doux is kind and cute.
Demons aren't that bad after all.
Of course demons are bad!
Those demons are tricking you!
Jeez, you're annoying!
We've prepared a better place and
better houses for all of you!
So shut up and come with us!
What?!
C'mon!
R-Right...
Oh, no!
This is heaven.
Unlike the demon world, this is a paradise
in the sky where divine
messengers, the angels, live.
Man, those villagers were weird.
They really didn't seem
to agree even in the end,
but there's no way they could be
happy being ruled by demons.
But Lord Mayu, please don't
resort to such force.
Why not?
Why not? That was practically kidnapping.
That's not what I'm talking about!
Why do we angels, divine messengers,
have to sneak around hiding from demons?
I don't think we were exactly sneaky.
The demons started this fight!
We might as well face them head-on!
I'll do it myself!
I'll defeat all the demons
and end this battle!
You mustn't, Lord Mayu!
Your Majesty!
Please calm down!
This is bad...
What's going on?!
Oh, Lady Jahi!
Why is His Majesty so angry?
Apparently, some angels stole away
some slaves from his domain.
Angels?! They enrage His
Majesty like nothing else.
We must quell his anger somehow.
If we let him continue, the
castle will be destroyed!
Hm? L-Lady Doux?!
Big Sister Jahi, let's go draw outside.
SKETCHBOOK
Lady Jahi!
C-Can you go draw by yourself today?
His Majesty and I have an
urgent matter to attend to.
Papa, too?
Y-Yes, His Majesty, too.
Okay! Good luck at work!
You mustn't wander too far off.
And make sure you come
home before it gets dark!
Okay!
"LET'S DRAW"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: NAOKI YANAGISAWA
SONG: DOUX
Colorful crayons
And some white paper
Let's draw
Let's draw all the things we love
A pointy mouth (Pointy, point, point)
A wriggly stem (Wriggle, wriggle, wriggle)
Leaves that grow and grow
A hungry flower
Some fluffy clouds
The sparkly sun
I wonder who that is.
You're in my way, stupid mongrels!
Hi, I'm Doux!
You dumb kid! Don't get so close to them!
We'll play again later, puppies.
Bye-bye!
Huh?
Here.
R-Right. Thanks...
What's a kid like you doing there?
This is a dangerous forest
near the demon castle.
No kid should come here alone!
Doux comes here all the time.
Huh? What're your parents doing?
Oh, fine. I'll take you home.
Though if I fly, the guys at
the demon castle might spot me.
So I guess we're walking.
Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
Safe?
Just shut up and I'll
protect you. Follow me!
A donut!
I don't have any snacks with me.
Let's go! Don't wander off.
SKETCHBOOK
Doux! Don't pull any pranks
at times like this!
Okay!
Well, that did actually save us but...
Yeah!
But one wrong move, and you might've been
hurt. Then, we couldn't go anywhere.
Then if the demons show up...
They'll be really nice.
Huh?
They're always really nice to Doux.
No way! Demon's aren't nice to humans.
But Doux isn't human. Doux is a demon.
Huh?
Y-You're... a demon?!
Yup!
You tricked me?!
No, I didn't.
So this is how demons do things!
I'm... I'm not gonna fall for that!
Ah! A butterfly!
Take that! And that! And that!
Butterfly!
Why you...
Are you okay?
Y-You're not bad...
D-Dang...
You can heal wounds?
Did the ouchie fly away?
I-It's not like it hurt
in the first place.
Hey, are you an angel, Big Brother Mayu?
B-Big Brother?!
Big Sister Jahi told me about them!
Angels live in the sky and
have wings and donuts!
Th-This isn't a donut! It's a halo!
So you can't eat it?
No!
Huh...
What're you drawing anyway?
An angel. Because it's the
first time I've seen one.
Huh?
Man... you're weird.
I am?
You're a demon, right?
Yup.
Demons are supposed to be bad guys
who fight us angels...
but you keep helping me.
You're fighting?
You don't know?
Angels are trying to make
the world peaceful,
so they don't get along with the
demons, who keep doing bad things.
Demons and angels used to fight every day.
But now...!
Now, demons do whatever they want while
angels sneak around helping people.
That doesn't solve anything!
That's why...!
I came here to defeat all the
demons and put an end to this!
Real fights mean hitting
your opponent head-on!
I think... making up is the real fight.
So Doux wants make up with the angels.
Th-That's not possible!
Angels hate demons,
and demons also hate us...
Wait, this drawing...
Doux likes you!
Wha...
There he is!
Lord Mayu! You mustn't be here!
Now there's lots of angels!
Then promise me, D-Doux!
I'm... I'm gonna be the
king of heaven someday!
So you become the king
of the demon world!
Doux is gonna be the king
of the demon world?
W-Well, if you become king,
you can do whatever you want.
So...
Um, wh-when that happens, um...
W-Well, it's a promise, okay?!
When that happens, the angels
and demons can make up!
Got it?! It's a promise!
Yup! A promise!
Your Majesty! We will bring back
the people who were taken from us!
Without fail!
I see... You're right.
Indeed.
But of course!
I'm home!
Look, Papa!
Wh-Wh-What's the matter, Your Majesty?!
Wait, Lady Doux?! Why's
there an angel drawn here?!
Papa's birthday's soon.
So here's a present.
That didn't answer my question!
His Majesty is absolutely
livid because of the angels!
Wivid?
Livid!
And this is just adding
fuel to the fire...
Y-Your Majesty! Please calm down—
Doux!
What?!
You drew this all for me?
Did I do good?
You did! You're the best in the world!
Rather than being angry
at the angel drawing,
his happiness from his birthday present...
Totally won this round!